Guide to the Charles A. Hanna Collection circa 1822–1950 (bulk, circa 1900–1950) MS 3126
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Publications by others, 1822–1950
  - Sale, Edith Tunis. "Interiors of Virginia Houses of Colonial Times", 1927 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-164)
  - Scots' Charitable Society of Boston. Constitution and By-Laws, 1878 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-147)
  - Sheafer, P. W., ed. "Historical Map of Pennsylvania", 1875 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-162)
  - Shotwell, Ambrose M., comp. "Annals of Our Colonial Ancestors and Their Descendants; or, Our Quaker Forefathers and Their Posterity", 1895–97 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-157)
  - Simmendinger, Ulrich. "The Simmendinger Register. True and Authentic Register of Persons Still Living... who in the Year 1709... Journeyed from Germany to America or New World.. .", 1934 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-152)
  - Simpson, Matthew, ed. "Cyclopædia of Methodism." Fifth revised edition, 1882 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-158)
  - [Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick.] "A Brief Account of the Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick; with Biographical Notices of Some of the Members, and Extracts from the Minutes", 1844 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-146)
  - Stone, William L., ed. "Washington County, New York: Its History to the Close of the Nineteenth Century", 1901 (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-106)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. I (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-100)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. II (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-101)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. III (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-102)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. IV (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-103)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. V (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-104)
  - Taylor, James. "The Great Historic Families of Scotland." Div. VI (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-105)
  - Tennyson, Alfred, Lord. "Maud Locksley Hall and Other Poems", 1891 (Offsite-box 16, Volume SN-108)
  - Tiffin, Edward. "A Memoir of a Man who Should Occupy First Place in the History of the State" (Offsite-box 18, Volume SN-128)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. I, 1946–1947 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-75)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. II, 1947–1948 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-76)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. III, 1948–1949 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-77)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. IV, 1949–1950 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-78)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. V (incomplete), 1950 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-79)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. VI (incomplete), 1952 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-80)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. Fifth series, vol. XV (incomplete), 1961 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-81)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. New series, vol. XXV (incomplete), 1944–1945 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-82)
  - Transactions of the Bibliographical Society. The Library. New series, vol. XXVI (incomplete), 1945–1946 (Offsite-box 14, Volume SN-83)
  - Turnbull, William B. "Scottish Parochial Registers. Memoranda of the State of the Parochial Register of Scotland, Whereby is Clearly Shown the Imperative Necessity for a National System of Regular Registration", 1849 (Offsite-box 19, Volume SN-161)
  - Loose publications, 1891–1948 (Offsite-box 35)
    • Abbott, Willis J., et al. "The Nations at War," 6 parts (1914)
    • Catalogue of Indian Exhibits Company
    • Curtis, Edward H. "Manual of the First Presbyterian Church, Lincoln, Nebraska" (1891)
    • Dawes, Charles G. "Address of Charles G. Dawes Before the Union League Club, Chicago: The Dangers of the Federal Reserve Law" (1915) [2 copies]
    • Dawes, Charles G. "Response of Charles G. Dawes to Subject 'The Sherman Anti-Trust Law and its Relation to the Public'" (1906)
    • Dawes at Home and Abroad
    • Dawson, Lawrence H. "A Book of Battles and Sieges"
    • From the Scottish Historical Review (October 1904)
    • Harbord, James G. "Invasion" (1944)
    • Harbord, James G. "Serving With Pershing" (1944)
    • Klett, Guy S. "The Scotch-Irish in Pennsylvania" (1948)
    • Maxim, Hudson. "Morris Canal Abandonment Problems: A Plea for the Abandonment of the Morris Canal and a Plea for the Preservation and Dedication of Lake Hopatcong"
    • New Jersey Historical Society. Constitution and By-Laws (1907)
    • Ohio Society of New York, 1885–1945, Directory
    • "Old Northwest" Genealogical Quarterly, vol. 4, no. 2 (April 1901)
    • "Old Northwest" Genealogical Society. Constitution and By-Laws (1898)
    • Proceedings of Clearing House Examiners and Managers Conference Held at Chicago Convention, American Bankers Association, September 29, 1924
    • Report of a Special Meeting of the Union League Club of New York with the Resolutions and Report Submitted by the Special Committee on Immediate Defense and National Service (1917)
    • Roberts, William Henry. "A Sketch of the History of the Presbyterian Church in the United States of America from the Earliest Times to the Year 1887" (1888)
    • Root, Elihu, et al. "Addresses by Elihu Root, James Duncan, Charles Edward Russell and Charles E. Hughes Delivered at the Reception to Mr. Roots at the Union League Club of New York City, August 15, 1917"
    • Rufus Fearing Dawes
    • Shaw, G. Bernard. "Common Sense About the War" (1914)
    • The Story of New Orleans, 1811–1911
    • Supplement to Burton Historical Collection Leaflet, vol. 9, no. 5 (May 1931)
    • Ulster-Irish Society Year Book, 1939
    • Walter Edwin Frew: Resolution Adopted by the New York Clearing House Association (1941)
    • Ye Old Canoe Place Inn, Hampton-Bays, New York
    • Zieber, Eugene. "Rules for the Proper Usage of Heraldry in the United States, and Other Extracts from the Popular Authority, Heraldry in America"